>> Kyle Simpson: 让我们深入练习练习此模块模式
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's dive into an
exercise to practice this module pattern
我们刚了解到的
that we've just learned about.
在此练习中，您将重构一些用于管理的代码
In this exercise, you are gonna be
refactoring some code that manages
讲习班的登记记录。
the enrollment records for a workshop.
你不会改变功能的但是
You're not gonna be changing
the functionality, but
你将会重新整理代码以使用我们所学到的经典
you are gonna be rearranging the code, to
use what we learned about the classic or
显示模块模式。
the revealing module pattern.
作为奖励顺便说下
As a bonus, by the way,
也可以自由地尝试使用 ES6 模块语法重新编写此命令，
feel free to also try re-writing
this using the ES6 module syntax,
在你做了这个练习的原始版本之后
after you've done the original
version of the exercise.
所以你的指示在这里应该比较直白
So, your instructions are laid out here,
it should be fairly straightforward but
您的指示信息包括定义模块工厂功能
your instructions include defining
a module factory function
叫做 defineWorkshop ，将会
called defineWorkshop,
that's going to make and
返回表示公共 API 的那些对象实例。
return those object instances
that represent the public API's.
这五种方法或功能是公共 API上需要公开的内容，
These five methods or functions are what
needs to be exposed on the public API,
你就会被定义为那些函数
and you're going to end up
defining those functions.
这些是不存在的。
So these are ones that don't exist.
你会把它们暴露在公共 API 中然后定义它们
You're gonna expose them in
the public API and then define them.
您将移动当前注册和 studentRecords
And you're going to move
the currentEnrollment and studentRecords
阵列到模块中，但它们必须是模块内部的空数组。
arrays into the module, but they need to
be empty arrays inside of the module.
然后你就会从外面去使用 addStudent 和
And then you're going to from
the outside use the addStudent and
enrollStudent 函数将数据推送到模块实例，好吗 ?
enrollStudent functions to push the data
into your module instance, okay?
所以我们不会把数据嵌入一个没有任何意义的模块
So we're not gonna embed data into
a module that doesn't make any sense,
或硬编码数据到模块中。
or hard code data into a module.
因此，您将在此处将所有这些分配更改为函数调用。
So you'll change all of those assignments
to the array into function calls here.
然后我们要用这个 defineWorkshop 制作一个模块
And then we're going to use that
defineWorkshop to make a module
称为 deepJS的实例。
instance called deepJS.
然后我们会多次打电话给deepJS.add留学生，
Then we'll call deepJS.addstudent multiple
times to add in the student records,
我们会打好几次叫 deepJS.enrollStudent 来登记
we'll call deepJS.enrollStudent
several times to enroll them.
然后我们会改变对其他可执行文件的引用
And then we will change the references
to the other executables,
有关 deepJS 模块 API的对应项。
to their counterparts on
the deepJS module API.
这就是你在做什么的概观。
So that's an overview
of what you're doing.
如果你看看 EXJS 文件这就是它的样子
if you look at the EXJS file,
this is what it looks like,
其功能在底部，通常被拆分和吊装。
the functions are at the bottom, and
generally they are split out and hoisted.
你只是把这个文件不改变它的行为本身
And you're simply taking this file
not changing it's behavior per se,
但将其格式化为模块。
but formatting this as a module.
你想从这里得到的好处是
The take away that you're trying
to get here is the advantages of
模块模式，正在隐藏不需要公开的详细信息。
the module pattern, are hiding details
that aren't necessary to be exposed.
没必要
It is not necessary for
任何人都知道阵列是跟踪当前注册的内容。
anybody to know that an array is what
is tracking the current enrollments.
或者有一系列物体跟踪当前的学生记录。
Or that there's an array of objects
tracking the current student records.
这是一个实施细节，
That is an implementation detail, and
所有软件工程的方式都是隐藏的
all manner of software engineering
tells that ought to be hidden.
所以它可以是未来重构的，所以它不能被滥用。
So that it can be future refactored,
so that it can't be abused.
所以这里的想法是使用模型模式来隐藏需要的详细信息，
So the idea here is use the model pattern
to hide the details that are necessary,
只会暴露那些需要的公共 IP 方法
only expose those public IP
methods that's necessary.